In this operation, everyone has a part to play.
Operation Fortune: Ruse de Guerre is a action, comedy,
thriller film directed by Guy Ritchie.
Special agent Orson Fortune and his team of operatives recruit one of Hollywood's biggest movie stars to help them on an
undercover mission when the sale of a deadly new weapons technology threatens to disrupt the world order.
Orson, played by Jason Statham.
Sarah, played by Aubrey Plaza.
Nathan, played by Cary Elwes.
Greg, played by Hugh Grant.
Danny, played by Josh Hartnett.
JJ, played by Bugzy Malone.
Operation Fortune: Ruse de Guerre is a 2023 spy action comedy film directed by Guy
Ritchie, and written by Ritchie, Ivan Atkinson, and Marn Davies.
The film stars Jason Statham, Aubrey Plaza, Josh Hartnett,
Cary Elwes, Bugzy Malone and Hugh Grant.
The film is about a spy, Orson Fortune (Statham), who must retrieve a stolen high-tech
device before an arms dealer (Grant) can sell it to the highest bidder.
Operation Fortune: Ruse de Guerre was theatrically released in international territories on
January 4, 2023, and theatrically released in the United States on March 3.
It was released digitally on Amazon Prime Video
in the United Kingdom on April 7.
The film explores themes of martial arts, london,
england, showdown, madrid, spain, espionage.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.